So one of the things that I'm really trying to do here on this social media thing is bring you guys voices that have impacted my knowledge base, my information space that are outside of traditional media that don't necessarily have, you know, big platforms, but they have big thoughts.
And Jeff Amell is one of those people. I feel like his predictions for things really be on point.
What this U.S. fascist regime fails to understand is that repression always leads to more radicalization.
The TikTok man bill revealed three things about the United States.
One, they don't care about free speech. Two, they don't care about free trade.
And three, they don't care about passing any laws that actually help their citizens.
I saw this coming from a mile away. Canada is copying the United States in potentially banning TikTok.
No doubt the EU and the UK are not far behind. I called it.
So tomorrow I'll be doing a YouTube live with Jeff Amell.
That's going to be on Thursday, March 21st at 12 p.m. Pacific, 2 p.m. Central.
And we're going to be talking about the TikTok ban because his predictions have come to pass.
And I'm like, you got any more in there, Miss Cleo?
So join us on YouTube live. The link is here in my stories and we'll see you there.